I apologize for missing my schedule appointment last time.
That's our.
We'd like to make it up now.
Thank you so much for today.
And for giving us this community.
To be a part of to enjoy and to participate in.
And I've created you and how our leaders with wisdom.
Thank you so much for today.
And for giving us this community.
To be a part of to enjoy and to participate in.
And I've created you and how our leaders with wisdom.
And discernment as they they lead us well.
And help us as citizens to do.
Everything we possibly can to make this a better place.
And I pray that you would guide us in the light of your kingdom,
which is putting others first.
And so we want to.
We want to live that way.
I pray that you do that in every one of us.
And so you bless us meeting this evening.
Would you give us your vision and your wisdom to do the things you want to do.
Ask all this in Jesus.
Amen.
Come on.
Would you be a pleasure.
My pleasure.
Relations to the fly of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for Wise of Science.
One nation.
And in the visible.
With liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Item four is presentation.
The municipal electric systems.
Hope a home or a drake or an extra machine or some ward.
Two customers.
The supervisor.
Your head through.
We're going to delay that.
Okay.
The next meeting.
Because of this weather.
We were on the phone with Tom Wright of this morning.
And it's just better that nobody has to travel.
Sure.
That's so.
There's one table.
Item five is public input.
And then schedule personal appearances.
And when the audience was to address the authority.
On the union agenda.
Item six.
The consent agenda.
Staff is recommending.
Item seven.
Item nine.
The consent agenda.
If there are no questions on the.
Those items.
And I'm going to take a motion to approve.
That's recommended.
Looks to approve.
And a second please.
Go call.
All right.
Four.
Move it.
All right.
Item ten is accepted.
Reset also.
The Sophie's work order.
Number.
Eight.
Five.
Nineteen.
Nine.
Seven.
Four.
Twenty.
Five.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Two.
Five.
Seven.
We're going to bring a party to you guys at June 4th.
So they're going to help us to do that.
We've been working on that.
In those revolving, long, fun, long is for this project.
Well, we're actually going to be this part of the project in house, but I mean, there's other projects like the sort of portion of that project
So I'll go ahead and do that.
Why is this same progress in Dr. Oport being curious?
We did, it's not really just for Jamie and it's for everybody out there.
Out there.
There's a way to run.
Okay.
We've also committed that once something goes in the spec building will be providing services to that as well.
Any questions on any of that?
Do we have a little visitor?
A limit on this?
Yes, sir.
So the limit is the RMS-163,000.
Okay.
I can't.
I'm a developer.
Just for a moment of life today.
Thank you.
We're going to have a motion to accept work order 18 slash nineteen national.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
18 nineteen national.
I'll make a motion.
And a second.
Second.
Yes, sir.
So this is for any of their help for construction oversight.
So whenever we bring the transfer guarantee into the testing on them,
we'll need the construction for some of the jobs just to help de-staff.
And time wise, where are we on those free.
are we on those projects?
So the transformers are being built.
They should, the first one should be coming in July.
And then we got everything back from legal last week
thus far as for the construction portion of it.
It's exactly the bus work, the wiring and everything.
Also making those changes this week.
So we should have it out for a bit the first and next week.
So then you'd say 30 days after that,
we'll have to come to the table and come to the table.
Number two.
Yes, sir.
So I mean, it's getting there.
It's just been a phase and then a final phase will bring to you,
will there be the construction and the breakers
and the final phase will be skated so we can want everything remotely.
And this work can increase the reliability of our system.
Yes, sir.
And it's also, as part of this, they will design the construction
of plants.
I mean, some things change on the field, that things are built.
So this way, though, any changes will make them to the plants.
So that way, 20 years from now,
whenever somebody wants to fix something, it's not like if I, you know,
the currently 1973, so we're trying to figure out what's going on.
So.
OK.
In the other questions on item 11, do we have a motion to accept the work order
18 slash 19 dash 9, and I'll second that workholders.
OK.
Should we move this type of question?
Board start.
OK.
Thanks, Tyler.
Any new business?
Staff reports during the practice dance available to give you questions
Any person can in the announcements
We on talk at all about the club in the projection like I thought maybe under managers comments
So we'll wait on that and I don't think he's a job. I should earn a second